Lawrence Guyot, Jr. 130
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Howard University, 1998-2008 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2008 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets - Booklet, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Newsclippings, 1998-2008 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Board of Zoning Adjustments, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2002-2008 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1998-2008 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Ward 1, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 1998-2002 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Board of Directors' DC USA Selection Meeting, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1996-2002 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Columbia Heights, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Blend Business Plan, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - DNC Rules and Bylaws Committee, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Kathy Simo - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - How to Develop Difficult Neighborhood Projects, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2002-2008 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - National Management Association New Member Packet, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Packet, 1993-2008 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 4th Quarter 2004 Report of Financial Activity (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Putting the Movement Back Into Civil Rights Teaching: Draft for Review 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Putting the Movement Back Into Civil Rights Teaching: Draft for Review 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Guyot's News You Can Use, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-2002 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1995-2004 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2003-2006 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Flyers, 2000-2012 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 2003-2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Heights, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2011 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Handouts/Brochures/Programs, 2001-2012 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings, 1999-2009 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1986-1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Magazines, 1999-2007 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Time Person of the Year: Obama Magazine, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Step Forward for Children, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Legal Documents, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Roll Call Hearing: C and Y Inc. t/a Royal Liquors, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Protest Hearing: C and Y Inc. t/a Royal Liquors 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Protest Hearing: C and Y Inc. t/a Royal Liquors 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Show Cause Hearing: C and Y Liquors t/a Royal Liquors, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Protestant's Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law: C and Y Inc. t/a Royal Liquors, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Neighborhood Action, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Prison Poetry, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - The Social and Political Context of the Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - LM: Modern Day Voter Suppression, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Race, History and Politics in the Nation's Capital by Bernard Demczuk, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Fannie Lou Hamer Statue Committee- Mission Statement (Draft), 2009 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Professional Development Course: Civil Rights Workshop, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Voices from the Struggle: A Collection of Guest Lectures, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Department of Human Services Office of Early Development, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Caroline Olsen interview of Lawrence Guyot, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Faith Matters, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Teaching for Change: Building Social Justice Starting in the Classroom, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - The Chaney Goodman Schwerner Justice Coalition, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - North Mississippi Rural Legal Services, 2005-2010 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Eyes on the Prize Dispute, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Annotated Program Script: "Peace, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Putting the Movement Back Into Civil Rights Teaching: A Teaching Guide for K-12 Classrooms, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - The Role of the Police Service Area: Policing for Prevention Handbook, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1 B Meeting Notes, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Mary Washington College Today Magazine, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Howard University, 1988-1997 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1999-2012 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1 B Meeting Notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - DC Democracy Fund Packets, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 14th World Festival of Youth and Students, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2001-2007 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Land Disposition and Development Agreement, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - How to Develop Neighborhood Projects, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Loose Printed Material, 2001-2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia Democratic State Committee, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Articles and Newspapers, 2000-2006 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Howard University Community Association, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Howard University-Team Focus Forms, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Halcomb v. Pickle, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Community Development, 2003-2007 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2000-2003 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Testimonies, 2001-2007 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Quarterly-1996 Democratic Convention (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Catalogues, 2000-2006 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Community Development Voter's Guide, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Board of Zoning Adjustment Application 16330, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Stop Church Burnings, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Childhood-Rappoteur's Report, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - The Voting Rights Act, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - African American Issues and Development, 2003-2006 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Stokely Carmichael to Kwame Ture, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Oral History: Lawrence Guyot, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Voting Issues, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Street Furniture Program, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Columbia Heights Ventures (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Columbia Heights Ventures (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Fourteenth Street Urban Renewal Area (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Fourteenth Street Urban Renewal Area (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Fourteenth Street Urban Renewal Area (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1999-2005 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Constitution of the United States of America, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Equitable Development in Shaw, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Howard University, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Association, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Heights, 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Government of the District of Columbia Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Government of the District of Columbia Office of the Chief Financial Officer, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Department of Human Services Office of Early Childhood Development, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1996-2003 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Council of the District of Columbia Notice District of Columbia Law 6-10 "Rental Housing Act of 1985" (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Magazines, 1999-2006 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Newsclippings, 1999-2006 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Informational Handouts, 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Programs, 1989-2003 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Flyers/Pamphlets, 1986-2003 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Presidential Inaugural Parade Ticket, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2008 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Shelter Proposal Before the Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - National Capital Revitalization Corporation Act of 1998 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Government Operations Newsletter, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - A Community-Based Plan for the Columbia Heights Metro Station Area, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1999-2005 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Field Video Production, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Afro-American Cultural/Technological/Scientific Olympics, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Confidential Organization Audit Coalition for the Homeless, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Briefing on Department of Human Services' Reorganization of Executive Direction and Support, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Proposed District of Columbia Apprenticeship and Training Act of 2001, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - American Slavery in History and Memory, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - By-Laws of the Ward One Democrats, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - The Piernas Family 1991 Calendar (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Coalition for Political and Financial Accountability, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Metrorail Installation of Canopies, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1999-2002 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Ward One Democrats, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Flyers, 1994-2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2009 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Programs/Biographies, 2005-2010 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings, 1999-2010 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 2004-2009 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Informational Handouts - Magazines, 2001-2009 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Howard University, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment Board, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2005-2009 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1996-2009 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1996-2002 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Northern Mississippi Rural Legal Services Greenville Office, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Mississippi Civil Rights, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - GAP Inc. Financial Statements, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - 4th Street NW Draft Traffic Calming Study, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Solitude: An Exploration of Benefits of Being Alone by Christopher R. Long and James R. Averill, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Obtaining Zoning Approvals in the District of Columbia, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Board of Directors DC USA Selection Meeting, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Guy Mason Homeless Shelter Debate 1 of 2, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Guy Mason Homeless Shelter Debate 2 of 2, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Uptown Destination District, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Duke: Draft Development Framework for Restoration of the Historic Jazz District, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Columbia Heights, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1996-2002 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Columbia Heights New Horizon Partners, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissions, 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2004 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Government of the District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1991-2004 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1999-2005 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - District of Columbia Historic Preservation Plan, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - McMillan Sand Filtration Site Revitalization Recommendations, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Roizman Development Inc., 1996 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Magazines, 1992-2004 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings, 1994-2010 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Flyers/Brochures, 1996-2005 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Informational Handouts, 2008-2010 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Howard University, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Association, 1997-2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1998-2001 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Division, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - District of Columbia Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - District of Columbia Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs Building and Land Regulation Administration, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 1345 Bill to Establish the District of Columbia Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Save the Streets - Stop the Guns Proposal, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Georgetown University Recipient Characteristics, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1C, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Washington Gas Correspondence, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Crime Prevention Conference, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - District of Columbia School Board of Education Transition Planning Team, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - The Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee Experience- Passing it on!, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Archaeological Investigation Conducted as a part of the Review Process for Construction of a Rite-Aid, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Printed Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Office of the District of Columbia Auditor and DC Action for Children, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Columbia Heights Assessment, 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission Manual, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Final Report on the Likely Social and Economic Impact of Rent De-control, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Tivoli Theater Site, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Bolchrist Development LLC Proposal for the Disposition of Parcel 19, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999-2003 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Land Disposition Agreement Public Hearings on Parcel 26, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - District of Columiba Neighborhood Market Drill Down, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Revialitzation, 1997-2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Heights Ventures Proposal to the Redevelopent of Sevel Parcels in the 14th Street Urban Renewl Area 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Columbia Heights Ventures Proposal to the Redevelopent of Sevel Parcels in the 14th Street Urban Renewl Area 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Ward One Democrats Inc., 2003 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2011 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, 2007-2011 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Programs/Handouts, 2002-2006 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Neighborhood Revialitzation, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1998-2003 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Revdelopement Land Agency, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Howard University, 2004-2011 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Newclippings, 1999-2009 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Magazines 1 of 2, 1997-2010 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Magazines 2 of 2, 1997-2010 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Council of the District of the Columbia, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2004-2005 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Mail-In Voter Registration From 1 of 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Mail-In Voter Registration From 2 of 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - MetroVoice Youth Entrepreneurs Program Inc., 2005 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - District of Columbia Historic District Preservation Plan, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Southern Elections Fund Inc. Program Report, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Summary Work Reports/Analysis/Evalutaion: Mobile Resource Team Project C.N., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Title I Funds Manual For Parents of Educationally Deprived Children, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Supreme Court of the United States Ricci v. DeStefano, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Re-Elect Commissioner Lawrence Guyot, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Dickerson - Jim Whitelaw Hotel Interview, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Wesley Hogan - The Politics of Patience, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - The Civil Rights Project Harvard University, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Implementing the Help America Vote Act: Helping to Avoid Discrimination, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Memorandum: Municipal Corporations, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1996-2006 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Community Development Plans, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - One Hundred Fourth Congress of the United States of America, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Magazines and Catalogues, 2004-2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - DC Agenda, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ben's Chilli Bowl, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Uptown Destination District Scope, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Howard University Neighborhood Revitalization, 1989-1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The Barry Administration: One Year Later, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Community Corrections Facility Siting Advisory Commission, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Heights Development, 1991-2002 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2006 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Loose Printed Material, 1980-2002 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Voting Issues, 2001-2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - HUSA General Assembly Meeting, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation Form McComb Summit, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers and Articles, 1990-2010 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Legal Document, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Transcript of Preceedings D.C. State Health and Development Agency, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Comprehensive Reentry Strategy for Adults in the District of Columbia, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - WPFW Radio (1 of 3), 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - WPFW Radio (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - WPFW Radio (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Flyers and Loose Printed Material, 1994-2004 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Magazines and News Articles, 2000-2008 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Voting Rights, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989-2004 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Board of Education Swearing in Ceremony, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 1 of 2, 1989-2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 2 of 2, 1989-2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1995-2011 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Informational Handouts, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Flyers/Brochures, 1995-2011 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings, 1996-2009 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Magazines, 2004-2007 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Howard University, 1989-2007 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Heights, 1999-2006 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1998-2006 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 1998-2002 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - The Council of the District of Columbia, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Alcohol Beverage Regulation Administration, 1997-2004 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - District of Columbia Water and Sewer Authority, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education Election, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1995-2003 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1998-2004 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - McMillan Sand Filtration Site Revitalization, 2002-2005 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Photocopies of a Photo of a Woman, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Supreme Court of the United States Peter G. Farina v. Board of Regents of the State of Florida, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Lawrence Guyot - Resume, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - U Street Revival, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - GAP INC. Management Letter Preliminary Draft, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Washington Regional Network for Livable Communities, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - How to Develop Difficult Neighborhood Projects, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Stand Up! Council on African American Affairs Contact List, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - 4th Street Northwest Draft Traffic Calming Study, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Youth Leadership Support Network, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Newsclippings, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Howard University Community Association Informational Packet 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Howard University Community Association Informational Packet 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Challenge and Contest to the Credentials of the Delegates of the "Mississippi Democratic Party" to the 1968 Democratic National Convention (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Uptown Destination District Study Area, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Washington Enrichment and Cultural Arts Network Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - North Capitol Neighborhood Development Inc., 2001 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - The Report of Surveys in Ten States, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - District of Columbia Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Act of 1995, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1974-2008 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Flyers, 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Informational Handouts, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings, 1999-2009 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Magazines, 2003-2007 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Howard University, 1998-2009 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Associations, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Heights, 1996-2009 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1998-2003 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2003 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - District of Columbia Office of Planning, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1997-2003 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2001-2005 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2003-2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)